

SUMIT KAMBLE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Phone: 7798042167

Email:Sumitkamble1252@gma

il.com

Portfolio Link

SUMMARY

Well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Handles any part of process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 1.8 years of related experience.

WORK EXPERIENCE

 ALOHA TECHNOLOGY PVT LTD, PUNE (NOV 2022 -PRESENT)

FULL-STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

- Work with aloha technology as full stack developer from Nov 2022.
- Work with various technologies with the team of 12+ developers, wrote code that was well-structured, tested, readable, and maintainable.
- Investment Application: Investment portal web-based and mobile applications, which provide online investment and offline investment plans for investors, have different modules for both users.
- Salon Management Application: A web-based salon management application that provides online appointment booking for clients and a mobile application that provides online beauty product sales.
- Banking Application: Work on an application that provides banking products, such as online loans and credit cards, for the user to help find the best credit cards and loans with his profile.

CLARITECH SOLUTIONS JAN 2022 – SEP 2022 / PUNE.

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER INTERN

- Remain updated with advance techniques with the group of 15junior developers.
- Wrote code that was well-structured, tested, readable, and maintainable.
- contributed to the development of six or more applications; and
- Contributed to the creation and application of system architecturedesigns and methods.
- ReactJS was used to create a web application and component.

Social Links:

GitHub Link:

https://github.com/LernTo Grow

Linked In Link:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sumit-kamble-7382a9190/

Education

MCA (2020-2022) (79%) At YSPM's Yashoda Technical Campus Satara

BCA (2017-2020) (67%) At Sangola Collage Sangola

Technical Skills:

Web Technologies: HTML 5, CSS 3, Bootstrap5
, Jsp, ReactJS, Ajax.

Back-end Language: -Java, JavaScript

Database: -

MySQL, SQL Server, Mongo db.

Backend Frameworks: Hibernate, Servlets, Nodejs,
ExpressJS.

Version Control: - Git.

IDE: -

Eclipse, Microsoft Visual Studio.

Web Servers / Runtime Environments: -Apache2, NodeJS.

Contact Details:

Address: Vishal nagar, pune Pin-411027